Rockville Journal World War II Letters
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Machowski, Frederick J, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mackowski, Frederick J, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Machowski, Frederick J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - MacMahon, John C, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; JAP Prisoner,MIA; Son of M&M R MacMahon,Wife Caroline; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Magdefrau, Edmund A, undated; France; Service w/ Supply Forces,Amphibious Trucks; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Magnuson, Roger, undated; AAF; Italy; Working on Plane Engine; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Maguire, Earl J, undated; Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Magura, Michael, undated; Atlantic City; NJ; Back from Europe, Ready for Reassignment; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mahr, Mary J, undated; Belgium; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Maizon, Francis A, undated; Shriveham; England; Attending English University; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Malesko, Edward V, undated; Chicago; IL; Promoted; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mamuszha, Edward S, undated; Holland; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mamuszha, Edward S, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mamuszha, Edward S, undated; Camp Polk; LA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mamuszha, Edward S, undated; Camp Polk; LA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mancheck, Leonard J, undated; Pacific War; Military Service; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Manchuck, Leonard J, undated; Jacksonville, FL; Camp Life; Carrier Base at Ribault Bay; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Manchuck, Leonard J, undated; Newport, RI; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Manchuck, Leonard J, undated; DeLand,FL; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mandelbaum, Daniel, undated; FPO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mandelbaum, Daniel, undated; College Station,TX; City Life; New Orleans,LA, Mardi Gras; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mandelbaum, Oscar, undated; Great Falls, MT; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mandelbaum, Oscar, undated; Spokane,WA; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mandelbaum, Daniel, undated; USS Hancock; Notes About Service; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mannel, Robert G, undated; Fort Dix; NJ; Assigned to 69th Infantry Division; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mantak, George L, undated; San Fransisco,CA; Scenery; Surfing at Waikiki,HI; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mantak, Francis J, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mantak, George L, undated; Anna Mantak; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mantak, George L, undated; 39th Bombardment Group; Guam; Commendation; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mantak, George L, undated; Guam; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Marcus, Nathan, undated; Japan; In Occupied Japan; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Markham, Wilbur W, undated; Miami Beach; FL; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Marley, William P, undated; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Marley, James T, undated; Camp Lee,VA; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Marley, William P, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Marquis, Louis S, undated; FPO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Masichuk, Harry, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Masichuk, Harry, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Masicuik, Harry, undated; Pacific Fleet; Military Service; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mather, Ted M, undated; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mather, Walter, undated; Paris,France; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; Camp Sibert; AK; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; New Orleans; LA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; Fort Benjamin Harrison; IN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; Fort McClellan; AL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; On Furlough, Shirley Barrette; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; Promotion, Mrs Fred Mathewson; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; Fort Devens,MA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; Camp Pickett, VA; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; Jacksonville, AL; Spanish Moss; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; Dorset; England; Worked in Army Hospital; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mathewson, Clifford W, undated; 106th General Hospital; England; Ward Master in English Hospital; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mattarelli, Henry, undated; Pearl Harbor; HI; Returning Home; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mattern, Kenneth R, undated; Mansfield Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mattis, Francis J, undated; Camp Pickett,VA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mattis, Bruno M, undated; Coolide,AZ; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mattis, Bruno M, undated; Camp Haan,CA; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mattis, Bruno M, undated; Fort Ord, CA; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mattis, Bruno M, undated; Camp Bowie,TX; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mattis, Bruno M, undated; Camp McCoy,Wi; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mattis, Bruno M, undated; Fort Leonard Wood,MO; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mattis, Bruno M, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Slatu Is,Prison Guard; Son of Mrs Sophie Mattis,23 River Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Matyia, Leonard, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - May, Guerino G., undated; Quonset Point, RI; Naval Air Station; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - May, Guerino G, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Son of M&M August May,East Main Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mayer, Ernest J, undated; Anzio Beach; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Maynard, Edward, undated; Los Angeles,CA; Scenery; Sierra Madre Range; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mayo, Arthur E, undated; Pyote; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mayo, Arthur E, undated; Harlingen,TX; Queretaro Building; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mayo, Arthur E, undated; Pyote Army Air Field; TX; Finished Training as B-29 Crew Member; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Mayo, Arthur E, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - McCantry, Charles S, undated; Fort McClellan; AL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McCarthy, Chris, undated; Fort Mc Clennan, AL; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McCarthy, James A, undated; Sampson; NY; Finished Basic Naval Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McCormack, George W, undated; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McCormack, George W, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 60 High Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McCracken, Stanley, undated; New Delhi; India; Received Award; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McDonald, Elmer R, undated; West Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McDonald, Richard, undated; Sampson; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McDonald, Richard, undated; Okinawa; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McDonald, Richard, undated; Davisville; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McDonald, John T., undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed Saipan,21; Son of M&M Alexander McDonald,Brook St; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McDonald, Elmer R, undated; Mrs McDonald; Request for Paper; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McDonald, Richard, undated; Mrs George McDonald; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McDonald, Richard, undated; Mrs Gladys McDonald; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McFarlane, Henry J, undated; Daniel Field,GA; Humor; Fort Bragg,NC; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McFarlane, Henry J, undated; Keesler Field,MS; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McFarlane, Henry J, undated; Daniel Field,GA; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McFarlane, Henry J, undated; Biloxi,MS; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McFarlane, Henry J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 78 Brooklyn Street; Son of Mrs William McFarlane; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McFarlane, Henry, undated; 8th Air Force; On List of 8th AF after VE Day; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McKone, Frederick W, undated; US Naval Reserve; Naval Air Navigator,Oahu, HI; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McKone, Frederick W, undated; Pearl Harbor; Returning Home; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, Edwin C, undated; England; with Clipping Gordon Denson's Mission; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, Edwin C, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, Edwin C, undated; Lubbock; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, J E, undated; Gulf Port; MS; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, J E, undated; Evirnetok Atoll; Marshall Islands; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, J E, undated; Camp Endicott; Davisville, RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, Richard L, undated; FPO San Francisco; CA; Overseas Hospital; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, Francis E, undated; Camp Perry; Williamsburg,VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, Harold J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, Richard L, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, Francis E, undated; Okinawa; Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, Harold J, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McLaughlin, Harold J, undated; New Guinea; Military Service; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McManus, Joseph P, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McNulty, Francis J, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McNulty, James, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed Munich,27; Son of M&M Charles McNutly,Wife Jesse; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McNulty, John J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McNulty, James, undated; Bradley Field; CT; Wife Receiving Medal for Husband MIA; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - McNulty, James, undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meacham, James W, undated; Camp Parks; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meacham, James W, undated; FPO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meacham, Raymond E., undated; Camden; SC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meacham, Raymond E., undated; Shaw Field; SC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meacham, Raymond E., undated; Nashville,TN; Air Force; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meacham, James W, undated; Camp Endicott,RI; Seabees; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meacham, Raymond E., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meade, Kenneth J, undated; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meade, Russel C, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meader, Ray L, undated; Iwo Jima; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meader, Ray L, undated; Camp Parks; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meader, Ray L, undated; Port Hueneme; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mehr, Doris M, undated; Bronx; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mehr, Doris M, undated; Quonset; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mehr, Doris M, undated; New York; NY; Discharged Form with Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Menge, Luther P, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Menge, Luther P, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Menge, Carelton P, undated; San Antonio,TX; City Life; Mission San Jose; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Menge, Luther P, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Menge, Carleton P, undated; Camp Gruber; OK; Stationed at Hospital; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Merkel, Robert, undated; Mrs Charles Merkel; Discharged; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mertan, Andrew, undated; Pacific Ocean; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mertan, Andrew, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mertan, Andrew P, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; North Africa and Pacific; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mertan, Steve J, undated; Pearl Harbor; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Merton, Stephen J, undated; Guam; See Mertan, Steve J; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Merton, Stephen J, undated; Guam; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Merton, Stephen J, undated; Hawaii; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Merton, Stephen J, undated; Hawaii; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Merton, Stephen J, undated; Guam; Playing Baseball for a Seabee Team; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Metcalf, Frank H, undated; Warrensburg; MO; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Metcalf, Frank H, undated; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meupert, Elmer, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mewton, D, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Meyer, Evelyn Mae, undated; Corporal; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Middleton, John W, undated; Graduated West Point; Legion of Merit Award; Comm Office Chinese Training Center; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miffitt, Julius, undated; San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miffitt, Julius, undated; 8th Army; Japan; Serving in Occupied Japan; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miffitt, Julius, undated; Manila; Philippines; Serving with 235th Engineer Combat Bat; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mifitt, Arthur, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mikalonis, Alphonse B., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Milanese, Carleton H, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Milanese, Clarence W., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Alphonso J, undated; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Donald J, undated; APO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; San Antonio; TX; Cadet Center - Newsletter; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; San Antonio; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; San Antonio; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; Chanute Field; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; Shanghai; China; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; Cincinnatti; OH; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; Greensboro; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Lewis J, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Lewis J, undated; Gowen Field; Boise, ID; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Lewis J, undated; Laredo; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Walter J, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Alphonso J, undated; Fort Leonard Wood,MO; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Russell, undated; Keesler Field,MS; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Russell, undated; Keesler Field,MS; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Harry A, undated; Fort Sheridan,IL; City Life; Hotel Sherman, Chicago; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Russell, undated; Fresno,CA; Hammer Field,CA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Irwin, undated; San Fransisco,CA; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Russell, undated; Keesler Field,MS; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Harry A, undated; Miami Beach, FL; Scenery; Coral Gables,FL; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Walter J, undated; Fort Bliss,TX; Scenery; El Paso,TX; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Walter J, undated; El Paso,TX; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; Frederick Army Air Field; OK; Graduated as Bomber Pilot; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Richard E, undated; Pyote Army Air Field; TX; Completed Flight Training; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Alfonso J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; West Main; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Irwin, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Russell, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Walter J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; West Main; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; George Field; Lawrenceville, IL; Arrived to Begin Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Gordon W, undated; San Antonio; TX; In Flight Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Lewis J, undated; England; Finished Additional Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, William M, undated; Hawaii; Letter to Parents about Death; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Russell E, undated; Europe; Continuing Military Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, Russell E, undated; Air Force; England; Finished Stay at Recreational Facility; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miller, William M., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miner, Clarence E, undated; Framingham; MA; Cushing General Hospital; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miner, Lewis W, undated; San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Miner, Lewis W, undated; Southwest Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, George, undated; Western Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, George, undated; Okinawa; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry S, undated; Shanghai; China; See Minor, Henry or Henry W; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry S, undated; Bookhill; SC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry W, undated; Camp Pickett; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry, undated; Smyrna,TN; Air Force; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry, undated; Fort Meyers,FL; Camp Life; Gunnery School; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry, undated; Tampa,FL; Florida; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, George, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, George, undated; Mrs Henry Limberger; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry, undated; Mrs Henry Limberger; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry, undated; Mrs Henry Limberger; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry, undated; Mrs Henry Limberger; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry, undated; Margaret J Minor; Returning Home; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry, undated; Mrs Harry Griffin; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Minor, Henry W, undated; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Misaiko, Alexander, undated; St Dizier; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Misaiko, Alexander, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Misaiko, Frank, undated; San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Misaiko, Alexander, undated; Fort Leonard Wood,MO; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Misaiko, Frank, undated; Camp Peary,VA; Seabees; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Misaiko, Frank, undated; Gulfport,MS; Seabees; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Misaiko, Alexander, undated; 75th Infantry Division; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mitchell, Erwin, undated; Sampson NY; Completed Training; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Mohr, Frederick C, undated; 83rd General Hospital; England; Recovering from Battle Wounds; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Donald F, undated; Tokyo; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Donald F, undated; Manila; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Donald F, undated; Tokyo; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Richard A, undated; China; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Frank, undated; Muroc,CA; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Donald F, undated; Mrs Arthur Morganson; Change Address,Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Donald F, undated; Mrs Arthur Morganson; Change of Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Donald F, undated; Mrs Arthur Morganson; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Harold M, undated; Mrs Arthur Morganson; Change of Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Harold M, undated; Mrs Arthur Morganson; Change of Address, Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Harold M, undated; Mrs Arthur Morganson; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Richard A, undated; Mrs Arthur Morganson; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Richard A, undated; Mrs Arthur Morganson; Change of Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)
  - Morganson, Richard A, undated; Mrs Arthur Morganson; Change of Address, Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Mc-Sh)